summitbank.com.pk 2019-05-08

# Website Privacy Policy | Summit Bank

####  Website Privacy Policy

##### Website Security and Privacy statement

  * About this Security and privacy statement
  * Acceptance and changes to Security and privacy statement
  * Security of information
  * Information collected
  * Collection of IP addresses
  * Cookies
  * Web Analytics
  * Tracking and Advertising
  * How we handle e-mail
  * Third party software
  * Use and disclosure of information

##### About this SUMMIT BANK Website Security and Privacy statement

This Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement apply to this website (“Summit Bank website”, “www.summitbank.com.pk”) which is operated by Summit Bank Limited.  
Summit Bank understands and appreciates that you, asSummit Bank website visitor, are concerned about your privacy and about the confidentiality and security of information we may gain about you online. We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement explain how your information will be treated as you access and interact with the Summit Bank website.  
As technology evolves, we will continue to strive to provide you with better, and more customized services and with a more effective website. We encourage you to review the Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement periodically because it may change from time to time.  
The Summit BankPrivacy Statement is contained in the Summit Bank General Terms and Conditions. It explains how Summit Bank generally protects your privacy and confidentiality and how Summit Bank treats your personal information, including any personal information collected in accordance with this Summit Bank Website and Security Statement.

##### Acceptance and Changes to Security and Privacy Statement

You acknowledge and accept that your use of the Summit Bank Website indicates your acceptance of the Summit Bank Website Terms of Use and the Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement.  
Summit Bank may at any time vary the Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement.

##### Security of information

Summit Bank takes reasonable steps to preserve the security of cookie and personal information in accordance with the Summit Bank Website Terms of Use and this Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement. If your browser is suitably configured, it will advise you whether the information you are sending us will be secure (encrypted) or not secure (unencrypted). If secure transmission is indicated, Summit Bank currently uses 128 bit SSL encryption.  
Summit Bank regularly reviews developments in security and encryption technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as totally secure. Accordingly, although Summit Bank strives to protect such information, Summit Bank cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we take reasonable steps to preserve the security of the information in our own systems.

##### Information collected

The information that Summit Bank collects about you is dependent on how you use the facilities offered by the Summit Bank website.

If you visit an unsecure area of the Summit Bank website (that is, an area where you are not required to log on) to read, browse or download information, our system will record the date and time of your visit to our site, the pages viewed and any information downloaded. However, our systems will not record any personally identifiable information.  
The Summit Bank website might offers a number of interactive facilities including tools such as live chat, calculators, online surveys and application forms.  
By using an interactive facility on the Summit Bank website you agree that Summit Bank may collect and retain any personal information that you enter when using these interactive facilities, and that we can use that personal information to contact you about our products and services and for any other purpose set out in the Summit Bank Privacy Statement. You agree that this applies even if you save, suspend or cancel the interactive facility, without submitting your information to us.  
Any personal information collected from the Summit Bank website will be treated in accordance with the Summit Bank Privacy Statement.  
We will not submit online application forms or online surveys without your consent.As per privacy protection and information security policy, Summit Bank never requests its customers to disclose the account number, Debit card information, user ID, Personal Identification Number (PIN), Telephone Identification Number (TIN), login and transaction passwords or any such information through e-mails. Any e-mail or written communication received by the customer, which appears to have been sent from Summit Bank seeking a customer’s personal and confidential information, should not be answered and Summit Bank should be advised.  
The Summit Bank website may also contain links to the websites of third party providers of goods and services (“Third Party websites”). If you have accessed Third Party websites through the Summit Bank website and if those third parties collect information about you, Summit Bank may also collect or have access to that information as part of our arrangements with those third parties. Summit Bank is not responsible for the content of Third Party websites. Links are provided for convenience only and do not represent any endorsement by Summit Bank of products offered by the site owner.  
Where you access a Third Party website from the Summit Bank website, cookie information, information about your preferences or other information you have provided about yourself may be shared between us and the third party. You cannot usually be identified from the information that is shared; if you can be identified from this information, we will seek your consent before sharing such information.  
Third Party websites should contain their own privacy statements and those third parties are responsible for their own privacy practices.

##### Collection of IP addresses

It is necessary for Summit Bank to collect your IP address for your interaction with various parts of the Summit Bank website. Your IP address is the identifier for your computer when you are using the internet.  
For instance, Summit Bank collects and stores your IP address when you log into Summit Bank Internet Banking. As part of our security for Summit Bank Internet Banking, Summit Bank uses this information when we attempt to detect and prevent fraudulent transactions in Internet Banking. We store your IP address for security, audit and reporting purposes. Your IP address will not be used by us or released to any third party except in the case of security, inappropriate behavior or fraud issues, such as unauthorized access to your, or our computer systems or fraudulent transactions.

##### Cookies

We use “cookies” as a fundamental part of our interaction with your Internet browser. The purpose is to provide you with better and more customized service and a more effective website. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on your computer, tablet or phone when you visit a website. A web server sends you a cookie and your browser accepts it. The browser then returns the cookie to the web server next time you visit that particular website. You can choose if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your preferences and options in your browser.Please note that if your browser is configured to reject all cookies you will be unable to use secure services on the Summit Bank website that require cookies in order to participate. Those services may include online applications and surveys. You may still be able to use some information-only pages even if you do not accept cookies.

##### Limited employee access to personal information

Summit Bank limits its access to your personal information to only those employees who hold a business reason for having access to such information. Summit Bank also educates all their employees about the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy. In addition, individual usernames and passwords are used by approved Summit Bank personnel to access your personal information online, providing audit trails to further safeguard the privacy of your personal information

##### How we handle e-mail

We will preserve the content of any e-mail that you send us, if we believe that we have a legal requirement to do so. Your e-mail message content may be monitored by our Summit Bank employees for security issues including where e-mail abuse is suspected; our response to you may be monitored for quality assurance issues.

##### Third party software

Summit Bank is not responsible for any third-party software used in conjunction with the Summit Bank website.

##### Use and Disclosure of Information

We will only use or disclose personal information or information generated by cookies in accordance with the Summit Bank Privacy Statement, specific and additional provisions relating to privacy which apply to certain areas of the Summit Bank Website and as otherwise set out in this Summit Bank Website Security and Privacy Statement.
